- ConversationTopicId: C10A_Patricia_M1
  PlayerPrompt: "@C10A_Patricia_TalkTo_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@C10A_Patricia_TalkTo_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: C10A_Patricia_PvP
  PlayerPrompt: "@C10A_Patricia_Prompt_PvP"
  NPCResponse: "@C10A_Patricia_Topic_PvP"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: C10A_Perseus_1_a
  PlayerPrompt: "@C10A_Perseus_1_a_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@C10A_Perseus_1_a_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: C10A_Perseus_1_S
  PlayerPrompt: "@C10A_Perseus_1_S_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@C10A_Perseus_1_S_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: C10A_Perseus_1_M
  PlayerPrompt: "@C10A_Perseus_1_M_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@C10A_Perseus_1_M_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: C10A_Perseus_1_C
  PlayerPrompt: "@C10A_Perseus_1_C_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@C10A_Perseus_1_C_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: C10A_Perseus_2_a
  PlayerPrompt: "@C10A_Perseus_2_a_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@C10A_Perseus_2_a_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: C10A_Perseus_2_S
  PlayerPrompt: "@C10A_Perseus_2_S_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@C10A_Perseus_2_S_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: C10A_Perseus_2_M
  PlayerPrompt: "@C10A_Perseus_2_M_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@C10A_Perseus_2_M_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: C10A_Perseus_2_C
  PlayerPrompt: "@C10A_Perseus_2_C_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@C10A_Perseus_2_C_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: C10A_Perseus_3_a
  PlayerPrompt: "@C10A_Perseus_3_a_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@C10A_Perseus_3_a_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: C10A_Perseus_3_S
  PlayerPrompt: "@C10A_Perseus_3_S_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@C10A_Perseus_3_S_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: C10A_Perseus_3_M
  PlayerPrompt: "@C10A_Perseus_3_M_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@C10A_Perseus_3_M_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: C10A_Perseus_3_C
  PlayerPrompt: "@C10A_Perseus_3_C_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@C10A_Perseus_3_C_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Dungeon_CutlassKeys00_Scalleywag_01
  PlayerPrompt: "@Dungeon_CutlassKeys00_Scalleywag_01_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@Dungeon_CutlassKeys00_Scalleywag_01_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Dungeon_CutlassKeys00_Scalleywag_02
  PlayerPrompt: "@Dungeon_CutlassKeys00_Scalleywag_02_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@Dungeon_CutlassKeys00_Scalleywag_02_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Dungeon_CutlassKeys00_Scalleywag_03
  PlayerPrompt: "@Dungeon_CutlassKeys00_Scalleywag_03_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@Dungeon_CutlassKeys00_Scalleywag_03_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Dungeon_CutlassKeys00_Mariner_01
  PlayerPrompt: "@Dungeon_CutlassKeys00_Mariner_01_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@Dungeon_CutlassKeys00_Mariner_01_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
